NIKUNJ JADHAV

nikunjjadhav786@gmail.com | +91 7977064992 | linktree/Nixk07 | linkedin/nikunj-jadhav

Profile

A skilled cloud associate with **2 years** of hands-on experience in enterprise-level IT Infrastructure Design, Continuous Integration, and Continuous Deployment (**CI/CD**) on **various cloud providers.**

Skills Certification

Programming Languages: C++, Java, Python, Bash Advanced Microsoft Excel: VBA, Macros, and Dashboards Databases: MySQL, SQL Services (SSIS, SSRS), phpMyAdmin

Version Control: Git, BitBucket

Web Development: **HTML5**, **CSS3**, **PHP**, **Yii2**, **Flask** Python Libraries: **NumPy**, **Pandas**, **Seaborn**, **Matplotlib**

Cloud Providers: AWS, Azure

Data Visualization Tableau, Power-BI
Pytorch-Deep learning | Dphi
Data Analysis with Python | Dphi
Azure Fundamental

Work Experience

Cloud Associate April 2022 - August 2023

SaphhireInfoTech Ventures Pvt. Ltd, Mumbai

- Worked as a **Cloud Associate**, creating daily reports in **Excel** & handling client mail & processing requests.
- Setting up application servers based on various requirements on the cloud while doing on-prem to **cloud migration**.
- Also helped create **disaster recovery plans** for various clients for an efficient system operational recovery to their DR site during a catastrophic app failure.
- Technologies: Azure, VM, Storage, S2S & more. AWS Services Like EC2, S3, Cloudwatch, VPC, Lambda, IAM etc.

Software Intern February 2022 - April 2022

Synergy Technology, Mumbai

- Built CRUD app with Admin Login, phpMyAdmin Database & Flask used with Foreign Key Tables for Music Webpage.
- From scratch built the plugin & added ease of use to the users & it's integrated within WordPress.
- Technologies: HTML, Javascript, PHPMyAdmin, PHP 7, Yii2, Flask.

Web-Development Intern

February 2019 - March 2019

- Sahu Technologies, Mumbai
- Designed Dynamic UI pages, for Hotel management systems and "Library Management Systems."
- Created a multi-page interactive website, linked it to a database, and deployed it using "PHPMyAdmin."
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHPMyAdmin.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology (BSc-IT), Mumbai University

2019 - 2021

• CGPA: 7.83/10

Diploma in Computer Science, Maharashtra State Board of Technical Education (MSBTE)

2016 - 2019

• 73%

Projects

Yoga Plus - IIT Bombay's EdTech Hackathon

- Developed an **Android** app & web app in **Flutter** that assists users in performing yoga and workouts by using machine learning models in **TensorFlow Lite** and user's stats were stored in **Firebase**.
- The web app uses the webcam to capture images and infers poses using the MAX deep learning model
- Technologies: HTML, CSS3, Javascript, Tensorflow.js, PoseNet, Model Asset Exchange

SOS-Android App

- Developed an **Android app** that triggers **SOS** via handset buttons without touching the phone screen
- It uses **voice recognition** to send an **SMS** when a certain word is spoken & then sends live location via SMS.
- Technologies: Java, Android Studio, XML, JDBC, and MS-SQL

Achievements Volunteering

Stood 7th in the IIT Bombay EdTech Hackathon Stood 3rd in the Apscript Hackathon Selected in CII - Debate Competition, State-Wise Youth Volunteer at HariPrabodham [2017-Present]